cfna.com 2017-02-03

# FACTS

                                                                                                              Rev. 10/2015
                        WHAT DOES CREDIT FIRST NATIONAL ASSOCIATION
 FACTS                  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                        Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
 Why?                   consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                        we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                        understand what we do.
 What?                  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                        have with us. This information can include:
                              Social Security number and income
                              account balances and payment history
                              credit history and purchase history
 How?                   All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                        business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                        customers’ personal information; the reasons Credit First National Association chooses to share;
                        and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                               Does Credit First National
 Reasons we can share your personal information                                               Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                   Association share?
 For our everyday business purposes—
 such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                          Yes                              No
 your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes—
                                                                          Yes                              No
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                       Yes                              No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                          Yes                              No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                          Yes                             Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                      Yes                             Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                       Yes                             Yes
                           Call 1-800-843-3449 and provide your name, account number, last four digits of your
                            Social Security number and phone number.
To limit               Please note:
our sharing            If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                       provide this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information
                       as described in this notice.
                       However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?             Call 1-800-321-3950

Page 2
What we do
How does Credit First National                    To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
Association protect my personal                   and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
information?                                      These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                                  and buildings.
How does Credit First National                    We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Association collect my personal
                                                      open an account or give us your contact information
information?
                                                      pay your bills or give us your income information
                                                      use your credit card
                                                  We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                  bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                    Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                      sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                                       about your creditworthiness
                                                      affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                      sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                  State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                  limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing for
an account I hold jointly with someone            Your choice will apply to everyone on your account.
else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                        Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                      Our affiliates include companies with a Bridgestone and Firestone
                                                       name, and nonfinancial companies such as Tires Plus, Wheel
                                                       Works, and Hibdon Tire.
Nonaffiliates                                     Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                      Nonaffiliates we share with can include independent retailers,
                                                       insurance providers, direct marketing companies, and merchandise
                                                       vendors.
Joint marketing                                   A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                                  together market financial products or services to you.
                                                      Our joint marketing partners may include insurance providers.
Other important information
If your billing address is in California, you have the right to limit our sharing of your personal information to our affiliates
(either for their own everyday business purposes or to market to you) and for joint marketing with other financial
companies. See the notice titled "IMPORTANT PRIVACY CHOICES FOR CONSUMERS.” If your billing address is in
California or Vermont, we do not disclose your personal information for nonaffiliates to market to you. If your billing
address is in Vermont, we do not disclose information about your creditworthiness for our affiliates’ everyday business
purposes or to market to you.
                                                                                                             CFNA 10/2016

PRIVACY AND THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE:
1. Use
Use of this website (the "Site") constitutes your consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this
Privacy Policy as modified from time to time by CFNA.
2. Registration
To use this Site, or certain portions or features of this Site, you may be required to first complete an online registration
form. During registration you may be prompted to provide to CFNA with certain personal information, including, but not
limited to, your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and account information. Becoming a registered user
enables you to review confidential account information for the service(s) for which you are enrolled and perform other
confidential transactions.
3. Browsing
If you browse this Site and have not registered, you are browsing anonymously. Personally identifiable information such
as your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address is not collected as you browse. However, your use of this Site
may be tracked, regardless of whether or not you have registered.
4. Cookies
One way your use of this Site is tracked is by using "Cookies" which are small pieces of information that are stored by
your Internet browser on your hard drive. A Cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer
viruses, or capture your e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information. Cookies allow us to recognize you
when you return to this Site and provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. Most web
browsers allow you to exercise control over Cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying
you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect
to disable this Site's Cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of this Site. Accepting Cookies is required if
you want to view personal or confidential information online, because they are essential for site administration
and security.
5. Log Files
This Site automatically collects information pertaining to your access. Such information may include your Internet protocol
("IP") address as well as other connection and usage information for system administration and troubleshooting purposes.
(An IP address indicates the location of your computer on the Internet.) CFNA does not link an IP address to any
personally identifiable information.
6. Changes to This Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2015, and updates and replaces any previous Privacy Policy for this Site.
If we decide to change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this Site so that you will
always be aware of what information we collect, use and distribute. Changes are effective when posted on this Site. You
should review this Privacy Policy from time to time to be aware of any such changes. Your continued use of this Site
indicates your agreement to any such changes. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please use the
"Contact Us" section of this Site.
7. Childrens' Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
This Site is a website directed to the general public. CFNA does not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal
information from children under 13.
8. E-mail
We may use your e-mail address to send you the following types of e-mail messages:
 Occasional updates about our products and services as well as CFNA marketing offers.
 Regularly scheduled e-mail newsletters related to CFNA products or services for which you have enrolled.
 Valuable offers from our business partners that we send you on their behalf.
 Service notifications related to your account(s).
All e-mail offers and e-mail newsletters sent to you by CFNA provide instructions on how to opt out of receiving future
offers or newsletters. These instructions are located at the bottom of the e-mail message. You may receive separate
newsletters pertaining to different CFNA products and services. In that case, you must reply to and decline the
newsletters individually. If you opt out, we will still send you e-mail with service updates as well as other important
information related to CFNA online products or services for which you are enrolled.

9. Transfer of Database
Please note that because a customer information database is customarily considered a business asset, CFNA reserves
the right to transfer the database in a merger or sale of some or all of its assets or in an action for bankruptcy. Your
information will continue to be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy by the acquiring or merged company unless
you are notified and provided an opportunity to change your preferences.
10. Data Security
This Site incorporates various physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your
personal information. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your
personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information.
11. User Name and Password
Many areas of this Site require that you log in with the use of a User Name and Password as an additional security
measure that helps protect your confidential information. This allows CFNA to verify who you are thereby allowing you
access to your account information and preventing unauthorized access.
When you have finished using a secure area of this Site, you should always click on the "Log Out" link that appears on
each secure page. By logging out you will end your secure session. No further secure transactions can be conducted
without re-entering your User Name and Password.
12. Caching
You should be aware that browser software often "caches" a page as you look at it, meaning that some pages are saved
in your computer's temporary memory. Therefore, you may find that clicking on your "Back" button shows you a saved
version of a previously viewed page. Caching in no way affects the security of your confidential User Name or Password. If
you use a computer in a public place to access your account information, simply quit/exit the browser software before
leaving to minimize the possibility of anyone else viewing your confidential information.
13. Linked Sites and Framed Pages
THIS SITE MAY INCLUDE LINKS TO THE WEB SITES OF THIRD PARTIES ("LINKED SITES"). THIS SITE ALSO
INCLUDES CERTAIN PAGES THAT ARE FRAMED TO PROVIDE INFORMATION FROM WEB SITES OF THIRD
PARTIES ("FRAMED PAGES"). CFNA PROVIDES LINKED SITES AND FRAMED PAGES AS A CONVENIENCE TO
THE VISITORS TO THIS SITE. THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINKED SITE OR FRAMED PAGE DOES NOT IMPLY
CFNA'S ENDORSEMENT OF ANY COMPANY, ITS WEB SITE, OR THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IT SELLS.
PLEASE NOTE THAT CFNA IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT, TERMS OF USE OR THE PRIVACY
PRACTICES OF ANY WEB SITE OTHER THAN OUR OWN SITE AND THE TERMS AND POLICIES OF THE PAGE
OWNER WILL CONTROL. CFNA HAS NO DISCRETION TO ALTER, UPDATE, OR CONTROL THE CONTENT ON A
LINKED SITE OR FRAMED PAGE. THERE ARE INHERENT RISKS IN RELYING UPON USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY
INFORMATION FOUND ON THE INTERNET, AND CFNA URGES YOU TO MAKE SURE YOU UNDERSTAND THESE
RISKS BEFORE RELYING UPON, USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY SUCH INFORMATION ON A LINKED SITE OR
FRAMED PAGE.
14. Advertising
CFNA may use third party companies to serve ads on this Site. These companies help CFNA execute, optimize, and
measure the effectiveness of our online advertising programs. These companies use Cookies and non-personally
identifiable information (for example, information that does not include name, address, e-mail address or telephone
number) about your visit to this Site to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide ads about goods and services
that may interest you. CFNA IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT, TERMS OF USE OR THE PRIVACY
PRACTICES OF THE ADVERTISEMENTS OR THE WEBSITES TO WHICH THEY LINK.
This Site's online advertisements and online applications may contain small graphics with tags in them. These tags are
not personally identifiable and work in conjunction with Cookies. These tags allow CFNA to measure the effectiveness
and response rates of our advertising.
